myloancare.in 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy – MyLoanCare.in

MyLoanCare Ventures Pvt Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “MyLoanCare.in or we/ our and including [www.myloancare.in](https://www.myloancare.in/) and MyLoanCare mobile app”) understands the privacy and confidentiality of its customers who have shared their personal information with us. It’s our top most priority to keep the information secure and avoid misuse of customer’s personal details.

Please find below the type of information we may collect from you and it’s usage for the services offered to you via our website and our business partners. This privacy policy is applicable to our current and existing and future customers. By visiting our website and registering with us, you agree to this privacy policy. 

By registering online at MyLoanCare or using our mobile app, you allow MyLoanCare and its business partners to get in touch with you via phone call, email or sms. The purpose of contacting you is to offer you our services for the product you have chosen, informing you about our new products, tell you about promotional offers running at MyLoanCare.in, or by its business partners and linked third parties. Under this policy, you authorize us to make contact with you for the above mentioned purposes even if your number is registered under DND/DNC/NCPR services. This authorization is valid until your account is deactivated by either you or us.

#### Personal Information

MyLoanCare collects personal information from its customers including first name, last name, email address, date of birth, your residence city and mobile number etc. MyLoanCare can also extract information from third parties or public shared profiles which are public in your social accounts. The collected information is stored at MyLoanCare only.

**Purpose**

MyLoanCare.in collects information from you when you register online with us or need some information regarding our products and services, visit our website. After registering with us or sharing personal details with us, you authorize us to contact you via email, call or sms and send you promotional offers.

**Use of Information**

MyLoanCare need your personal information for the following purposes –

  * to reply to your queries being submitted by you
  * process applications or orders submitted by you
  * in order to resolve problems with any services provided to you
  * to send you promotional offers, new products or services available on our website or third parties with whom we have a tie up 
  * manage or achieve our duties with subject to any contract with our business partners
  * information received from you is combined with the information we get from third parties in order to make our website and services better 
  * as mentioned in this privacy policy

**Information Disclosure and Sharing**

MyLoanCare.in does not sell/ rent or disclose your personal information with anyone as described in this policy. We may share your personal information with our business partners or with another entity in case of business merger or sale of MyLoanCare.in’s business part.   
We restrict the collection and use of your personal information. We may disclose your personal information in a non-personally identifiable manner that does not reveal your identity. MyLoanCare does not let anyone use your account information and any other personal identifiable information except some specific domestic procedures in order to manage, expand and improve our services. Third parties who have tie up with us can contact you and tell you about our services but with a limited access and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information as mentioned in the contract with us.  
We may share your personal information to the government agencies under the law in case of identity verification, investigation of cyber incidents, hearings and punishment of offences, or where disclosure of information is required for the legal purpose. We may also need to disclose the information to third parties under the law.  
MyLoanCare.in has various types of products like loans, credit cards offered by lenders and banks. If you apply for these products or services and disclose information to these providers then the use of your information is dependent on their privacy policies for which MyLoanCare is not responsible.

#### Tracking via Cookies

MyLoanCare and its partners use cookies to analyze trends, manage the website, improve marketing, track user’s preferences around the website and collect demographic figures for overall use. You can control the use of cookies at an individual browser stage by disabling these cookies that may restrict your use of certain features or services on our website.

#### Log Files

We use log files that include internet protocol (IP) address, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, exit or referred pages, date/time stamp, operating system to analyze trends and user’s movements while visiting the website. This information is combined with the other information we collect about you to improve our services, site functionality and marketing.

#### Email – Opt Out

If you don’t want us to send you emails or other promotion information, write us at [care@myloancare.in.](mailto:care@myloancare.in) It may take some time to process the request but once you are unsubscribed by us, you won’t receive emails or any other information from us.

#### Security

MyLoanCare.in use suitable technical and electronic measures to protect the personal information being submitted to us. In today’s time, we cannot guarantee complete security as no electronic system is 100% secure but we still use multiple security measures to protect illegal use, damage or loss of any kind of information. You must also maintain the confidentiality and security of your login id and password and may not share these credentials with any third party.

#### Connection to Other Websites

MyLoanCare.in provides links to other websites. The privacy of the information provided to other websites is not our liability. MyLoanCare.in is not responsible for any loss of personal information through other sources. We can only suggest you to read their privacy policies when you visit their websites.

#### Third Party Advertising

MyLoanCare.in uses ad agencies or third party advertising companies to provide ads when you are using our website. These companies do not use your personal information except the details about your visit to our website so as to offer ads on our websites as well as on other websites about the services that you may like.

#### Contact Us with Questions or Concerns or For Grievance Redressal

If you have grievance or complaint, questions, comments, concerns or feedback in relation to the processing of information or regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an e-mail to [care@myloancare.in.](mailto:care@myloancare.in) The name and contact details of the Grievance Officer is Mr. Santosh Kumar, MyLoanCare, MyLoanCare Ventures Pvt Ltd, B-38, Sector – 32, Industrial Area, Gurgaon 122003 India. 

Notice

The effective date of this Policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this Policy was revised or materially changed.

Effective Date

March 14, 2018
